EvilestDeath
The End of Evangelion
Blood on the Dance Floor - Suicide Club
havrd
Cowboy Bebop
Megamind (the movie) - Intro scene
Calvin3
Galaxy Angel
My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic sound clips
StarRodMan
Overman King Gainer
Johnny Bravo Theme Song
havrd
Angel Beats
South Park sound clips
LOLWTFBBQ
Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann
Watchmen - sound clip
Lmckay023
Fullmetal Alchemist Brotherhood
Super Mario bros 8 bit sound effects
Kaiyou1691
Lucky Star
Jason Steele -
Kurohei
Tengen Topa Gurren Lagann
Patient Zero - Dwarf Hole (Diggy Diggy Hole)
adracamas
Fruits Basket
Mitch Hedberg - Houses
IntegratedPaper
Clannad
Skyrim Sound Clip
N.P.C.C.
Dragon Ball Z
The Boondocks Sound Clip
Insignia
Highschool of the Dead
Tobuscus - Tobuscus Adventures
IntegratedPaper
The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya
Chris Tomlin - How Great is Our God?
Calvin3
Pani Poni Dash
Kindergarten Cop Sound clip
Dajore Niseny Elph
Sailor Moon Super S
Star Wars Episode 4: A New Hope Sound Clip
$ov13t
Poyno
Dave Rogers - Space Boy aka Initial D theme
LawRayLiet
Akikan!
The Whitest Kids U' Know - Grapist
ThatsNotMyName_studio
Elfen Lied
The Beatles - Lucy in the Sky With Diamonds
IntegratedPaper
Angel Beats!
Death Note Sound Clip
mattroks101
Darker Than Black
Fat Joe - Make It Rain
IntegratedPaper
Death Note
The Lonely Island - Threw It On The Ground
ThatsNotMyName_studio
Elfen Lied
Styx - Too Much Time On My Hands
Speedlemon
Panty and Stocking with Garterbelt
Eminem - Without Me
ThatsNotMyName_studio
Highschool Of The Dead
Pulp Fiction sound clip / The Centurians - Bullwinkle II