BeyondSandrock
Full Metal Alchemist
The Muppet Movie - Movin' Right Along
Tayson1570
Dragon Ball Z
Price Of Persia Parody
HalOfBorg
Highschool of the Dead
Red Dwarf - "Abandon Ship!"
Ryan Fornelius
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Queen - You're My Best Friend
Tank
High School of the Dead
G.I. Joe Theme
Bill Ein
Shijou Saikyou no Deshi Kenichi
Joe 'Bean' Esposito - You're The Best
Tayson1570
Full Metal Panic
Family Guy - Jackass Parody
HalOfBorg
Full Metal Alchemist
Alice Cooper - He's Back (The Man Behind The Mask)
Deemer
Goku Midnight Eye
GI Joe Spoof - Motorcycle sound clip
BlamKing
My Neighbor Totoro
Aerosmith - I Don't Want To Miss A Thing
BlamKing
Lucky Star
Talladega Nights sound clip
Tayson1570
Clannad
Suger Ray - When It's Over
Chewi105 & mattroks101
Death Note
Pong sound effects
Seasons
Inuyasha
Living in a Box - Living in a Box
Keinushi
Yu Yu Hakisho
Star Wars Episode IV: A New Hope - Jawa sound clip
The Last Visible Dog
Naruto
Ren & Stimpy sound clip
Peter Hopkins
Skip Beat
Lonely Island - On the Ground
scarmullet
Serial Experiments Lain
Little Nicky sound clip
Bill Ein
Rosario + Vampire, Disco Dancer
Parvati Khan - Jimmy Jimmy Ajaa