LawRayLiet
Cowboy Bebop
"Flintstones" Opening Theme
Robert Frazer
Canaan
Electric Six - High Voltage
Zarxrax
Adventures of Sonic the Hedgehog
The Beatles - I am the Walrus
Tayson1570
My Bride Is A Mermaid
Blue October - Into The Ocean
Humnut
Bokurano
Sublime - Date Rape
Bakagami & XelaisPWN
Toradora!
Hall & Oates - Maneater
Bill Ein
Naruto
Pif-paf, oy-oy-oy! - Opera
Santiago
Puella Magi Madoka Magika
Pink Floyd - Is there Anybody Out there
Robert Frazer
Oban Star-Racers
Kylie Minogue - Spinning Around
StormWolf
Cowboy Bebop: The Movie
Brandon Flowers - Crossfire
Malev
Azumanga Daioh
SUPER STAR -MITSURU- - She is my wife
Malev
Nausica? of the Valley of the Wind
Nobuo Uematsu - Chocobo Theme (Final Fantasy III DS version)
Malev
Panty & Stocking with Garterbelt
Michael Jackson - Speed Demon
Robert Frazer
Outlaw Star
Peter Gabriel - Solsbury Hill
BlamKing
Higurashi no Naku Koro ni Kai
Peachfuzz - Hero of Nineteen Eighty Three
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Godannar
The Beach Boys - Good Vibrations
LOLWTFBBQ
Tenjou Tenge
Antoine Dodson & The Gregory Brothers - Bed Intruder Song
Tayson1570
Tenjou Tenge
Five For Fighting - 100 Years
Prophet of Doom
Pokemon
Weird Al Yankovich - I Think I'm A Clone Now
BlamKing
My Neighbor Totoro
The Hobbit (1977 animated film) - Rollin' Down the Hole
Rspectcopyrightmyass
Sorcerer Hunters
The Addams Family Theme
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Hellsing OVA
Nice Peter - Nom Nom Nom Nom, Babies!
Robert Frazer
Mezzo DSA
Merv Griffin - I've Got a Lovely Bunch of Coconuts
LySs
Panty & Stocking with Garterbelt
Group X - Good Girl Yes!! Bad Girl No!!
!@#$ Youkai
Paranoia Agent
Daft Punk - Around the World
Backup
Azumanga Daioh
Talking Heads - Psycho Killer
Malev
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers - The Waiting
LySs
Panty & Stocking with Garterbelt
Cliff Richard - Devil Woman
SLAYER NEXUS
Green Green
Harry Belafonte - Day-O (The Banana Boat Song)
Backup
Death Note
Emigrate - Wake Up
Deemer
Azumanga Daioh
Weird Al Yankovic - Your Horoscope For Today
Chewi105
My Neighbor Totoro
Weird Al Yankovic - Another One Rides the Bus
HalOfBorg
Dragonball Z
Alan Jackson - Where Were You (When The World Stopped Turning)
VasSerMan7
Azumanga Daioh
Eminem - Just Lose It
LySs
Durarara!!
Basement Jaxx - Where's Your Head At?
Prophet of Doom
Naruto
A-Ha - Take on Me
Prophet of Doom
Pokemon
Mike Batt - Bright Eyes
HalOfBorg
Mahoromatic: Something More Beautiful
Patsy Cline - I Fall To Pieces
Shibbidah
The Melancholy of Haruhi-chan Suzumiya
Dead or Alive - You Spin Me Round
EvilestDeath
Cowboy Bebop, Naruto
Copycat - Copycat
BlamKing
Ponyo
Fastball - You're An Ocean
Rebbie
Pokemon
Willow Smith - Whip My Hair
Hosokawa37
Midori Days
Linkin Park - Figure.09
BlamKing
Howl's Moving Castle
Blink 182 - What's My Age Again?
Robert Frazer
Dennou Coil
Weird Al Yankovic - Virus Alert
Hosokawa37
Karin
Nickelback - Photograph
Robert Frazer
Sound of the Skies
Sabaton - Ghost Division
Robert Frazer
You're Under Arrest (OVA)
Axel F - Haltemeyer
Seasons
Planetes
Ramones - Gimme Gimme Shock Treatment
Synbad2
Gundam Seed
Franz Ferdinand - This Fire
Gan_HOPE326
One Piece
Ofra Haza - Deliver Us
LawRayLiet
Higurashi: When They Cry
Weird Al Yankovic - Good Old Days
LySs
Ouran High School Host Club
Blur - Girls & Boys
Celticfoxx
Blue Sub #6
The B-52's - Rock Lobster
Robert Frazer
Rebuild of Evangelion 1.11
TeddyLoid - Fly Away
Zarxrax
Akira
Shinedown - Sound of Madness
Hosokawa37
Panty & Stocking with Garterbelt
Disturbed - Down With the Sickness
Hosokawa37
Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann
Disturbed - The Night
VasSerMan7
Darker Than Black: Ryusei no Gemini
Grand Theft Auto 4 - "America's Next Top Hooker" Commercial
Shockweed831
Beelzebub
Sex Pistols - Anarchy in the U.K.
Shockweed831
Beelzebub
Marilyn Manson - Snake Eyes and Sissies
Hosokawa37
Soul Eater
Shinedown - Devour
Zarxrax
2x2 Shinobuden
Donovan - Mellow Yellow
Tayson1570
My Bride Is A Mermaid
WWE - Chris Jericho's theme
EvilestDeath
Excel Saga
My Chemical Romance - Dead!
Palla156
Clannad
Spongebob Squarepants - The Best Day Ever
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Panty & Stocking with Garterbelt
Peter Gabriel - Big Time
Palla156
Kingdom Hearts 2
Kanye West - Heartless
Tayson1570
Dragon Ball Z
Hootie and the blowfish - I go blind
Stevie
Naruto Shippuden
Jimi Hendrix - Foxy Lady
BlamKing
Negima!?
TLC - No Scrubs
Robert Frazer
Sky of Connection
Tomoyasu Hotei - Battle Without Honor or Humanity
emi-chan
Yamato Nadeshiko Shichi Henge
Rocky Horror Picture Show - Touch-a Touch-a Touch Me
LySs
Panty & Stocking with Garterbelt
Trey Songz - Panty Droppa
BlamKing
Azumanga Daioh
Badfinger - No Matter What
Hosokawa37
Fullmetal Alchemist Brotherhood
Disturbed - The Night
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Oruchuban Ebichu
"Dramatic Chipmunk" audio
StormWolf
FullMetal Alchemist
Eminem featuring Rihanna - Love the Way You Lie
BlamKing
Death Note
Paul Simon - Me And Julio Down By The Schoolyard
Hosokawa37
K-ON!
Eminem - Lose Yourself
Robert Frazer
Panty & Stocking With Garterbelt
Stan Bush - The Touch
Robert Frazer
End of Evangelion
Cream - Strange Brew
BlamKing
Azumanga Daioh
Garbage - Right Between the Eyes
EvilestDeath
Crayon Shin Chan
Tiger Army - Oogie Boogie's Song
Hosokawa37
Kanon [2006]
Dean Martin - Jingle Bells
BlamKing
Princess Mononoke
Divinyls - Wild Thing
Humnut
Clannad
Nightwish - Ghost Love Score
BlamKing
Castle in the Sky
Van Halen - Jump
Animal_Guy
Inukami
Cliff Edwards and the Hall Johnson Choir - When I see an Elephant Fly
LySs
Sayonara, Zetsubou-Sensei
Rockwell - Somebody's Watching Me
BlamKing
Chobits
Duran Duran - Electric Barbarella
HalOfBorg
Full Metal Alchemist
Bob Rivers - Chipmunks Roasting on an Open Fire
HalOfBorg
Puni Puni Poemi
Bob Rivers - Bob Rivers
Speedlemon
Panty and Stocking with Garterbelt
AC/DC - Dirty Deeds Done Dirt Cheep
MagicalSuicune
FLCL
Elvis Presley - Burning Love
scarmullet
Dragon Ball Z
Cheech Marin - My Scrotum
Darkzi
Clannad
Limp Bizkit - Hot Dog
Robert Frazer
Panty & Stocking With Garterbelt
Girls Aloud - Sound of the Underground
Malev
The Melancholy of Haruhi-chan Suzumiya
Weird Al Yankovic - The Night Santa Went Crazy
Speedlemon
Panty and Stocking
The Beatles - Come Together