Calvin3
Azumanga Daioh
Songify This - Winning by Charlie Sheen
MEECROB
The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya
South Park sound clip
havrd
JoJo's bizarre adventure
Chuck Berry - Riding along in my automobile
Tank
Dai Mahou Touge
Portal 2 sound clip
Dajore Niseny Elph
Bobobo-bo Bo-bobo
Katy Perry - Firework
Calvin3
Dragonball
SpongeBob Squarepants sound clip
havrd
Toki wo kakeru shoujo
Barrell Roll song
nyaakyle
Nichijou
Ferris bueller's day off sound clip
havrd
Death Note
Nancy Sinatra - Bang Bang
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Hellsing Ultimate
asdfmovie
havrd
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Queen - Somebody to love
havrd
The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya
Jackass 3.5 - sound clip
SilentChaz
Howl's Moving Castle
The Crazy World of Arthur Brown - Fire
ThatsNotMyName_studio
Highschool of the Dead
The Outlaw Josey Wales sound clip
Hosokawa37
Various
Right Said Fred - I'm Too Sexy
Robert Frazer
End of Evangelion
Maybelline "Sensational Red" Lipstick Commercial
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
K-On!
Squeeze - Tempted
mattroks101
Trigun
George Thorogood - One Bourbon, One Scotch, One Beer
jinzo64
Strike Witches
K-on! sound clip
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Toradora!
Family Guy - Surfin' Bird
Hosokawa37
Kore wa Zombie Desu ka?
System of a Down - Aerials
havrd
JoJo's Bizarre Adventures
The whitest kids you know - Russian roulette sound clip
Robert Frazer
End of Evangelion
ABBA - Under Attack
Zanmora
Yu Yu Hakusho
Kung Pow: Enter the Fist Sound Clip
havrd
Death Note
Eminem - Toy Soldiers
havrd
Kyoto Animation Commercial
The Hitchhickers guide to the galaxy - So long and thanks for all the fish