Introduction
Requiem - Dies Irae
Francesco Verdi
Zarxrax
Berserk
The Andy Griffith Show Opening Theme
SSGWNBTD
Twin Spica
Fantasy Spaceship
Creamy
Zarxrax
Azumanga Daioh
Mad World
Gary Jules
SSGWNBTD
Words Worth
Mr. Ed Opening Theme
Zarxrax
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Chop Suey
Richard Cheese
SSGWNBTD
MAPS
Maps
Yeah Yeah Yeahs
SSGWNBTD
Perfect Blue
Fuck Her Gently
Tenacious D
Nightowl
End of Evangelion
Bitches
Mindless Self Indulgence
SSGWNBTD
Evan Get It On
Tootsie Pop Commercial
Zarxrax
Cowboy Bebop, End of Evangelion
For Those About to Rock
AC/DC
SSGWNBTD
Barefoot Gen
"My Anus is Bleeding"
Sound clip from "Rejected"
Zarxrax
"Evangelion Opus" AMV by ShounenDizzyCow
Mountain Dew "Bohemian Rhapsody" Commercial
Zarxrax
Dragonball Z
"I Have a Dream" speech by Martin Luther King, Jr
SSGWNBTD
Barefoot Gen
Drop the Bomb
Scotty D
Zarxrax
Cowboy Bebop
Mmmbop
Hanson
Zarxrax
Ending (Azumanga Daioh)
Sound Clips from "Freakazoid"
Zarxrax