Masahiro & Sexximus
The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya
The Pretender - Intro
deathhunter101
Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica
P.O.D. - Boom
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Magical Shopping Arcade Abenobashi
Baltimora - Tarzan Boy
Shibbidah
Shinryaku! Ika Musume
Alestorm - Death Throes of the Terrorsquid
SilentChaz
Pom Poko
Transformers theme
Robert Frazer
Seitokai Yakuindomo
Savlonic - Tiny Japanese Girl
SilentChaz
Excel Saga
Jonathan Ian Mathers - Squirrel Songs
Calvin3
Dokuro-chan
Bloodhound Gang - Why's Everything Always Pickin' on me?
SSJGarfield
Lucky Star OVA
Jurassic Park sound effect
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Azumanga Daioh
mrweebl - Cat Face
Cheeze4brains94
Pokemon
The Notorious B.I.G. - Hypnotize
SilentChaz
High School of the Dead
Disturbed - Meaning of Life
Rebbie
Evangelion
30 Rock sound clip
N.P.C.C.
Sailor Moon
Dean Martin - That's Amore
chaoshusky
one piece
the Emperor's new groove sound clip
Masahiro & Sexximus
Death Note
Homestar Runner - Halloween 2001 Audio Clip
SuperiorAtolBoy
Excel Saga
Drew Carey's Improv-A-Ganza sound clip
havrd
Bakemonogatari
cash cash - jaw drop
keinushi
Higurashi no naku koro ni
coppercab - Gingers have souls
Robert Frazer
Panty and Stocking with Garterbelt
Tom Jones - Sex Bomb
ThatsNotMyName_studio
Excel Saga
Pirates of the Caribbean: Curse of the Black Pearl sound clip
frankyfilms
Baccano
Justice League Unlimited sound clip
adracamas
Bottle Fairys
Mitch Hedberg - Sandwiches
Dajore Niseny Elph
Pokemon
Garfield and Friends - Intro