Street Fighter II: Champion Edition (arcade game)
Zarxrax
Dragonball Z
Big Balls
AC/DC
Kitsuner
Serial Experiments Lain
All Your Base
The ECCNirvana
Fall_Child42
Azumanga Daioh
Hurt
Johnny Cash
rogueintellectproductions
Card Captor Sakura
The Van Man
Bob Chance
Chaosprojects
Magical Shopping Arcade Abenobashi
Just an Old Fashioned Girl
Eartha Kitt
Fall_Child42
Leave it to Piyoko
Hard Knock Life
Dr. Evil
Haunter103
Excel Saga
Dicks Don't Grow On Trees
Robyn Archer
Chaosprojects
Spirited Away
The Money Song
Monty Python
Fall_Child42
Chobits
Peanut Butter Jelly Time
Buckwheat Boys
Yokou Seishirou
End of Evangelion
Sound Clip
Planet of the Apes (1968)
AmPsy
Naruto
Katamari on the Rocks
Katamari Damacy
ngsilver
Tenchi Muyo
Spit (1) & spoken word (2)
John Murphy (1) & Verthandi (2)
dokidoki
Naruto
Log Theme
Ren & Stimpy
pat_hulse
Hellsing
Go Down to the Old Pub Instead
Stephen Lynch
rogueintellectproductions
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Yoshimi Battles the Pink Robots Pt. 1
The Flaming Lips
Chaosprojects
Various
Viscinity of Obscenity
System of A Down
Chaosprojects
Azumanga Daioh
I Like To Move It
Reel 2 Real
AmPsy
Dragonball
I'm So Ronery
Trey Parker
Haunter103
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Kiss
Prince
Szwagier
WXII: Patlabor Movie 3
Ordinary Day
Great Big Sea
ngsilver
Excel Saga
Bad Boys
Inner Circle
Haunter103
NieA_7
Radio Jingles for Tokyo's Inter-FM
Ben Folds
Fall_Child42
I My Me! Strawberry Eggs
Short Shorts
The Royal Teens
ImmortalArena
Elfen Lied
Boys in the Hood
Dynamite Hack
Qyöt27
Azumanga Daioh
Peach Pie on the Beach
Polysics
Deuce Loosely
Elfen Lied
Fucked Up Girl
The Vandals
AmPsy
Hale+Guu
The Coming Curse
Iced Earth
Chaosprojects
Di Gi Charat, Green Green
Albuquerque
"Weird Al" Yankovic
Haunter103
Cyborg 009
Hurt
Johnny Cash
BunofGovt
Maison Ikkoku
Crack Whore Mama
Mr Plow
mikestrife
Revolutionary Girl Utena
Big Balls
AC/DC
Haunter103
End of Evangelion
Yoshimi Battles the Pink Robots Pt. 1
The Flaming Lips
LuigiHann
Excel Saga
Hard Knock Life
Dr. Evil
Yukitosan
The Legend of Zelda
Albuquerque
"Weird Al" Yankovic
Perfect Chaos
Mai Otome & Azumanga Daioh
All Your Base
The ECCnirvana
Keiji-san
Kodomo no Omocha
Peach Pie on the Beach
Polysics
Chaosprojects
Sailor Moon
I Like To Move It
Reel 2 Real
Fall_Child42
Seven of Seven
The Van Man
Bob Chance
Haunter103
Revolutionary Girl Utena
Kiss
Prince
Strawberry Key
Mahoraba, Love Hina
Beer!
Psychostick
Vile2539
Elfen Lied
Albuquerque
"Weird Al" Yankovic
pat_hulse
Angelic Layer
Inside Your iPod #2: Salutations
Olde English
Strawberry Key
Pokemon, Digi Charat, Super Friends
I Like To Move It
Reel 2 Real
AMV4000
Berserk
Hurt
Johnny Cash
SSGWNBTD
Tree of Palme
Dicks Don't Grow On Trees
Robyn Archer
Fall_Child42
Card Captor Sakura
Boys In The Hood
Dynamite Hack
Chaosprojects
Cowboy Bebop
Ordinary Day
Great Big Sea
Szwagier
Pokémon the First Movie: Mewtwo Strikes Back
I'm So Ronery
Trey Parker
Strawberry Key
Elfen Lied, Happy Lesson, Love Hina, Neon Genesis Evangelion, End of Evangelion, Macross Plus, Oh My Goddess!, Please Teacher!, Please Twins, Please Twins!, RahXephon
Peanut Butter Jelly Time (1) & Sound Clip (2)
Buckwheat Boys (1) & Family Guy (2)
Qyöt27
Berserk
Splish Splash
Bobby Darin
teknoboy
Revolutionary Girl Utena
Viscinity of Obscenity
System of A Down
Strawberry Key
Gravitation
Albuquerque
"Weird Al" Yankovic
Dezbo21
Crusher Joe: Ultimate Weapon Ash, Project A-ko 2, Blue Gender, Neon Genesis Evangelion, Akira, Project A-ko, Crusher Joe (motion picture), Cowboy Bebop
I Want A New Drug
Huey Lewis & The News
RichLather
Revolutionary Girl Utena
Ordinary Day
Great Big Sea
Strawberry Key
Azumanga Daioh, FLCL, Kare Kano, Nurse Witch Komugi, Koop x AtomX/sea lion goodness
I Like To Move It
Reel 2 Real
Janzki