LySs
Baccano!
Richard Cheese - Last Resort
scarmullet
Evangelion
Clerks sound clip
DH1900
Elfen Lied
The Dark Knight sound clip
Humnut
Dokuro-Chan
Brutal Legend sound clip
JBFiLMz
Fullmetal Alchemist
Terminator 2 sound clip
Darkzi
Elfen Lied
Predator 2 sound clip
scarmullet
Haruhi
Live Action: Videodrome
scarmullet
Evangelion
Clerks sound clip
EvilBlackDarkness
Dead Leaves
s-CRY-ed sound clip
EvilBlackDarkness
Higurashi no Naku koro Ni
Necro Critic sound clip
Zachary Wisniewski
Elfen Lied
Jamie Kennedy and Stu Stone - Circle Circle Dot Dot
Darkzi
Magical Shopping Arcade Abenobashi
Mighty Boosh - Old Greg sound clip
Shirik
Excel Saga
Mongrels - What A Difference A Day Makes
Robert Frazer
Taishou Yakyuu Musume
Bull Durham sound clip
FORDboy357
Trigun
The Lonely Island (feat. Jack Black) - Sax Man
Hosokawa37
Puni Puni Poemi
Whose Line Is It Anyway? sound clip
Robert Frazer
Azumanga Daioh
Kill Bill Vol. 1 sound clip
Tank
Grenadier
Family Guy sound clip
Rebbie
Evangelion
DJ MTG - 6 Little Eggs
Tank
Bleach
Robot Chicken sound clip
BeyondSandrock
Voltron: Defender of the Universe
Tenacious D - Beelzeboss
Tazuto
Various
Zero Punctuation sound clip
Shirker
Ouran High School Host Club
Left 4 Dead sound clip
Doomimus
Hellsing Ultimate / Azumanga Daioh / Live Action: Twilight
Rifftrax - Twilight