Synbad2
Gurren Lagann
Spider Man theme song
SouthTexasTitan
High School of the Dead
300 sound clip
Prophet of Doom
Hare+Guu
Hall & Oates - Maneater
Fujhiton
Death Note
Super Smash Bros. sound clip
Celticfoxx
Evangelion
Jonathan Coulton - Re: Your Brains
Shirker
Gunslinger Girl
Dirty Harry sound clip
Rebbie
Yu-Gi-Oh! DM
The Guild - (Do You Wanna Date My) Avatar
Darkzi
Gurren Lagann
Invader Zim sound clip
SV.inc (Juno)
Death Note
Dj Hazard - Psichodelic
Blend That
Samurai Champloo
South Park sound clip
Rebbie
Azumanga Daioh
The Lonely Island - Jizz In My Pants
scarmullet
Ponyo
Army of Darkness sound clip
Tazuto
K-ON
Legend of Zelda overworld theme
Nygmatech Enterprises
Mitsudomoe
Robot Chicken sound clip
Moo
Lucky Star
Midori - Yukiko-san
Tazuto
Various
Robot Chicken sound clip
Tank
Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann Movie 2
A-ha - Take On Me
Tazuto
Naruto Shippuden
Legend Of The Dragoon commercial