Absolute_Apocalypse
Evangelion
Lonely Island - Like A Boss
CelticFoxx
Utawarerumono
Family Guy sound clip
Threvlin
Ghost in the Shell
"Weird Al" Yankovic - Virus Alert
Rebbie
Evangelion
Futurama sound clip
Tank
Naruto Shippuden
The Producers - Keep it Gay
FORDboy357
Fist of the North Star
Hillbilly Ninja sound clip, South Park sound clip
Raster88
Naruto Shippuden
Alice in Wonderland - Painting the Roses Red
Rebbie
Evangelion
Futurama sound clip
NegiTraudt
Code Geass
Family Guy sound clip
Austin Marck
Hayate No Gotoku
The Mighty boosh - Old Gregg
Tazuto
PetoPeto-san
LMFAO - Im in h-town trick
scarmullet
Chobits
Jon Etheridge - Prostitute Mickey 2
Humnut
Kodomo no Jikan
Venture Brothers sound clip
scarmullet
Evangelion
The Adventures of Sonic the Hedgehog sound clip