Doomimus
Azumanga Daioh
Monty Python - Argument
greensucksbluerules
Lily C.A.T.
Cake - Carbon Monoxide
Rebbie
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Futurama sound clip
Absolute_Apocalypse
Code Geass
Dead Kennedys - Kill the Poor
Doomimus
Azumanga Daioh
Monty Python - Argument
DXM
Hell girl
AC/DC - Dirty deeds (done dirt cheap)
scarmullet
Neon Genesis Evangelion
The Empire Strikes Back sound clip
Doomimus
Azumanga Daioh
Cannibal Corpse - Make Them Suffer
Oghma
The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya
George Carlin
Oghma
Higurashi no Naku Koro ni
Fine Young Cannibals - She Drives Me Crazy
scarmullet
Azumanga Daioh
Me, Myself, and Irene sound clip
Hosaka Enterprises
Space Runaway Ideon, The Ideon: Be Invoked
Spongebob Squarepants sound clip
Hockey-kun
Lucky Star
Dschinghis Khan - Moskau
scarmullet
Elfen Lied
Batman Beyond sound clip
Raster88
Pokemon
The Lonely Island - I'm on a Boat