Doomimus
Various
INXS - New Sensation
scarmullet
Dragonball Z
Ready to Rumble sound clip
Rebbie
Sasami Magical Girls Club
Matthew Wilder - Break My Stride
Keena53
Kuroshitsuji
Porgy and Bess - Bess, You is Mah Woman Now
Tazuto
Bokusatsu Tenshi Dokuro-chan
Spongebob Squarepants sound clip
Rhoran
IGPX: Immortal Grand Prix
Space Ghost sound clip
Austin Marck
Dennou Coil
The Lonely Island - Throw It On The Ground
The-Ville
K-On!
Led Zeppelin - Stairway to Heaven
scarmullet
When the Cicada's Cry-Higurashi
Family Guy sound clip
Akatissi
Yakitate!! Japan
Green Day - American Idiot
Doomimus
Princess Mononoke
Monty Python and the Holy Grail sound clip
Robert Frazer
Neon Genesis Evangelion
The Lancashire Hotpots - Bitter Lager Cider Ale Stout
scarmullet
End of Evangelion
The Shining sound clip
Absolute_Apocalypse
School Days
Kagami Seira - Super Special
Rebbie
Berserk
Miss Papaya - Supergirl
★☆★
Code Geass
Portal sound clips