LySs
Ouran High School Host Club
Renaldo Lapuz - We're Brothers Forever DANCE MIX
SouthTexasTitan
Azumanga Daioh
The Waterboy sound clip
Tank
Code Geass
Christina Aguilera - Genie In a Bottle
Tank
Bleach
Spongebob Squarepants sound clip
scarmullet
End of Evangelion
Conan: The Barbarian sound clip
Tazuto
Excel Saga
Evanesence - Going Under
Prophet of Doom
Tenchi Muyo
Red Dwarf sound clip
Rebbie
Neon Genesis Evangelion
The Door - The End, "Weird Al" Yankovic - Albuquerque
Prophet of Doom
Various
Family Guy sound clip
emi-chan
Ouran High School Host Club
SMA Commercial sound clip
StarRodMan
Aim for the Top! Gunbuster
Punch-Out!! Training Theme
Jen Star
K-On
Glee sound clip
Robert Frazer
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Thunderbirds Opening Theme
Stevie
Death Note
How the Grinch Stole Christmas - Mr. Grinch
scarmullet
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Nick Jr sound clip
Robert Frazer & fdYkn
Heroman
Prodigy - Voodoo People (Pendulum Remix), Fallout 3 sound clips