Oghma
Bokusatsu Tenshi Dokuro-chan
Aqua Teen Hunger Force sound clip
Drew199321
Cowboy Bebop
Pure Pwnage sound clip
Rastar
Bleach: Memories of Nobody
Will Smith - Men in Black
Doomimus
Azumanga Daioh
Barnes & Barnes - Fish Heads
Oghma
Berserk
The Waterboy sound clip
Somi
Higurashi no Naku Koro ni
TurboNegro - All My Friends Are Dead
Doomimus
Azumanga Daioh
Strong Bad E-Mail - "Replacement"
Hockey-kun
Death Note
Family Guy sound clip
ClosedPool
Code Geass
The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers - Requiem for a Tower
scarmullet
Neon Genesis Evangelion
He-man and the Masters of the Universe sound clip
Inkwolf
Princess Tutu
Todd Rundgren - Bang the Drum
Tempest
Oedo 808 Cyber City
Queen & David Bowie - Under Pressure
Doomimus
Azumanga Daioh
Disney's Pocahontas - Colors of the Wind
Hoodoo
Trigun
South Park sound clip
scarmullet
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Family Guy sound clip