Koolfox
Nichijou
5 Second Films - Late for Work
LawRayLiet
Panty and Stocking with Garterbelt
The Lonely Island - I Just Had Sex (feat. Akon)
LawRayLiet
Azumanga Daioh
YouTube clip - "Your face, goddammit"
Tayson
Elfen Lied
Justin Bieber - Never Say Never
Koolfox
Black Lagoon
System of a Down - Cigaro
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Dragon Ball: The Path to Power
The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time - sound clip
SilentChaz
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Time Gentlemen Please sound clip
LawRayLiet
Welcome to the NHK
Hollywood Undead - The Diary
Giliage
Mahou Shoujo Madoka Magica
Dick Figures - Butt Genie
LySs
Panty & Stocking with Garterbelt
Monty Python's The Meaning of Life - Every Sperm is Sacred
RBRat3
Yosuga no sora
Wet hot american summer sound clip
Lmckay023
Higurashi No Naku Koro Ni
Mock The Week - Scenes we'd like to see
santiago198
denpa onna seishun otoko
bloodhound gang - diarrhea runs in the family
LawRayLiet
Kannagi: Crazy Shrine Maidens
Black Eyed Peas - My Humps
LawRayLiet
Rozen Maiden
South Park sound clip
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Hellsing Ultimate
Day of the Dead sound clip
CelticFoxx
Welcome to the NHK
Tenacious D - Kickapoo
Bill Ein
Elfen Lied
Elfen Lied sound clip
Tank
Bleach
Bleach sound clip
brotherbear92
Azumanga Daioh
Jon Lajoie - WTF Collective
LySs
Tiger & Bunny
The Boondocks - A Pimp's Prayer
LawRayLiet
Elfen Lied
Sugarcult - She's the Blade
LawRayLiet
Girls Bravo: Second Season
Your Favorite Martian - Bitch Got a Penis
LawRayLiet
Baby Princess 3D Paradise Love
MadTV - World's Greatest (Statutory Rapist)
mattroks101
Azumanga Daioh
Pulp Fiction sound clip
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
My Last Day
Devo - Whip It