marbilSWE
Welcome to the nhk
Spose - I'm awesome
HaarTheDragonlord
Shin-chan
Code Monkeys - Sound Clip
ThatsNotMyName_studio
Fullmetal Alchemist
Disney's Beauty and the Beast - Gaston
SilentChaz
Interstella 5555
charlie teh unicron episode 2 - sound clip
N.P.C.C.
Fruits Basket
The Looney Tunes Show - We Are In Love
Patrick Wiley
Fooly Cooly
Men in Black - Sound Clip
SleeplessPanda (C.T.)
Fist of the North Star
Fleetwood Mac - Hold Me
jjlb84
Berserk
Army of Darkness - sound clip
ThatsNotMyName_studio
Elfen Lied
Melissa Manchester - Midnight Blue
N.P.C.C.
Neon Genesis Evangelion
Jem and The Holograms (The Misfits) - Congratulations
BakaLyte39K
Acchi Kochi
Chrono Trigger - Lavos' Theme
HaarTheDragonlord
Armored Trooper Votoms: The Last Red Shoulder
Family Guy - Sound Clip
adzman
Akira
Sealab 2021 - Sound Clip
HaarTheDragonlord
Sengoku Basara
Psy - Gangnam Style
Robert Frazer
Joshiraku
Full Metal Jacket - Sound Clip
HaarTheDragonlord
The Legend of Reyon: From New Struggles
The Boondocks - Sound Clip
ThatsNotMyName_studio
Excel Saga
FUN. - We Are Young
N.P.C.C.
Tenchi Universe
Terminator & Terminator 2: Judgement Day - Sound Clips
HaarTheDragonlord
Pokémon: Indigo League
Speedy Gonzales - Sound Clip
Robert Frazer
Shiki
Weebl's Stuff - science
N.P.C.C.
Queen's Blade
SpongeBob SquarePants - Sound Clip
ThatsNotMyName_studio
Excel Saga
FloRida - Whistle
N.P.C.C.
Cromartie High School and Night Shift Nurses Kazama Mana
The Lonely Island - Threw It On The Ground