Robert Frazer
My Ordinary Life
The Ren & Stimpy Show sound clip
Malev
The Sword in the Stone
m1dy vs M-Project - Squid vs Pantyhose
LawRayLiet
The Powerpuff Girls
Macy Gray - Slap A Bitch
bloodlover1987
Hey Arnold
Weird Al Yankovic - Do I Creep You Out
Pain
Asterix Conquers Rome
Disturbed - Indestructible
N.P.C.C.
Dexter's Laboratory
Michael Sembello - Maniac
Doomimus
Pocahontas
Imogen Heap - Hide and Seek
EvilestDeath
The Boondocks
Oli Chang - Chicken Techno
ssgwnbtd
Adventure Time
The Lonely Island - Falcor vs. Atreyu
Rspectcopyrightmyass
My Little Pony: Frienship is Magic
Starfox 64 sound clip
Malev
The Raccoons
Super Mario sound clips
Calvin3
SpongeBob Squarepants
Planet of the Apes sound clip
Doomimus
Ratatouille
Camille - Le Festin, Ratatouille Sound clip, Original audio
Chewi105
The Lion King
Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time sound clips
EvilestDeath
Time Squad
Black Tide - Warriors of Time
Doomimus
Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs
Randy Newman - Short People
Masahiro
Boondocks
Weird Al Yankovic - Don't Download This Song
LawRayLiet
My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic
TeddyLoid - Fly Away
LawRayLiet
Invader Zim
Weird Al Yankovic - Everything You Know Is Wrong
N.P.C.C.
JEM and The Holograms
Amy Winehouse - Rehab
EvilestDeath
Metalocalypse
Soulja Boy - Super Soak