Calvin3
Azumanga Daioh
Mentos Commercial
santiago198
Puella Magi Madoka Magica
Eminem - One Shot Two Shot
frankyfilms
Baccano
asdfmovie2 - I Like Trains segment #1
Lmckay023
K-on!
Lordi - Hard Rock Hallelujah
Calvin3
Chobits
Looney Tunes - Yankee Doodle Daffy sound clip
Tank
Highschool of the Dead
J.T. Machinima - I Bagged a N00b
Shibbidah
Clannad
Vitamin String Quartet - Through the Fire and the Flames (Violin Cover)
Calvin3
Dragonball Z
Katy Perry - Firework
Rebbie
To Aru Kagaku no Railgun
Bow wow wow - Aphrodisiac
Robert Frazer
Ookami-san and her Seven Companions
The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly - Il Buono, Il Brutto, Il Cattivo
Calvin3
Lucky Star
Homestar Runner - Teen Girl Sqad
Chewi105
Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood
The Script - Breakeven (Falling To Pieces)
Involdus
Ah my Goddess, Southpark
Hot Chip - I Feel Better
SleeplessPanda
Soul Eater
Dean Martin - Ain't That A Kick In The Head
Chewi105
Deathnote
O-zone - Dragostea Din Tei
synbad2
Gundam 00
Zulu - The Man with the Golden Gun
vejtornado
One Piece
Caramell - Caramelldansen
Robert Frazer
Puella Magi Madoka Magica
Pringles commercial
Calvin3
K-on
Savlonic - Electro Gypsy
N.P.C.C.
Dragon Ball Z: Bardock ? The Father of Goku
Sonic R - Can You Feel The Sunshine
humnut
He is My Master
Aqua Teen Hunger Force sound clip
StarRodMan
Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann
Dexter's Laboratory - You're Ridin' That Hog